arshtcenter.org 2017-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Adrienne Arsht Center

AA

Under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.

The Adrienne Arsht Center for the Performing Arts of Miami-Dade County (the “Center"), is subject to and complies with the Florida Public Records Act. Therefore, your information acquired via our Web site may be subject to disclosure. In the event that you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, except as stated below, unless required by state or federal law. Please note that Florida's public records law requires that all information received in connection with public business be made available to anyone upon request, unless the information is subject to a specific statutory exemption.

At the Center, we respect your right to privacy. We understand that users of the Center's Web site need to be in control of their personal information. "Personal Information" includes, but is not limited to, name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information. the Center adopted this Web site Privacy Policy to inform users of how the arshtcenter.org Internet site collects, stores, and uses personal information that is submitted via the Web site.

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

A. Anonymity and Credit Cards

You may purchase tickets and remain anonymous if you choose to pay by cash in person at our Box Office. Even if you purchase tickets with a credit card, your credit card information (as defined further herein) will not be disclosed to or shared with another entity.

B. General Information

You may visit and browse our Web site as often as you like without logging in, and in such instances personal information about your visit will not be collected. If you visit our Web site simply to browse, we may collect general information about the way in which you use our Web site, including, but not limited to, the time and duration of visit, type of Web browser used, the operating system/platform you are using, your IP address, the Web sites from which you linked to us, and other generic information. We also may note whether and how you use the Web site by recording site traffic patterns and click streams. We do not associate this general information that we collect with any personal information and we do not otherwise monitor this information on an individual basis. Instead, we aggregate this usage information and use it only to identify the levels and areas of interest in the Center and to improve and refine our Web site and services. We may perform (or have third parties perform), analyses of visitors' behavior, and may share aggregated, anonymous data with sponsors and advertisers.

C. Personal Information

the Center collects personal information when you submit personal information to the Center, make a purchase or a contribution, request information on our products and services, participate in a promotion or an online survey, contact the Center with a question or suggestion, apply for employment with the Center, and when you attend certain special events where heightened security is necessary. Depending on the nature of your interaction with the Center, we may ask you for information such as your name, phone number, physical address, company-related information, e-mail address, credit card information, including expiration date and billing address, and product preferences. Once you register with the Center and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Your Personal Information may be used by us (or third parties engaged by us) to: (1) customize the advertising and the content that you see (including, but not limited to use of retargeting and pixels); (2) fulfill your requests for products and services; (3) contact you,;(4) conduct research; (5) communicate information pertaining to an event at the Center (for example, time changes of a performance, traffic advisories); (6) send order confirmations; (7) update membership information; (8) respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; (9) establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; and, (10) other communications from the Center.

In addition, the Center may provide your name and address or phone number to third parties whose products and/or services we believe may be of interest to you (although we do not share any other information about you, the selection criteria may result in the third party being able to identify your relationship with the Center in a broad manner, i.e., that you are a subscriber or donor, or may have attended a particular production). You can request at any time that we do not share your name and address or phone numbers with such third parties, by calling the Box Office at 305.949.6722. the Center does not monitor or control, nor is it responsible for, the privacy policies of third parties.

D. Shared Information

Mailing address information is never sold, rented or freely given to any outside entity. Mailing address information may be traded with other nonprofit arts companies for a one-time usage through a third-party mail house. This is common industry practice. However, to request your account to be marked as "do not trade", please contact the Box Office at 305.949.6722.

E-mail addresses are never sold, rented or freely given to any outside entity.

the Center will share information with various entities, including but not limited to, community and cultural organizations (for example, chambers of commerce), as well as third parties and facility renters, which may produce or present certain performances at the Center for which you have purchased a ticket. Examples of these third parties include, but are not limited to, our Resident Companies (Florida Grand Opera, Miami City Ballet and New World Symphony), as well as third party rentals (The Cleveland Orchestra, Live Nation, Anschutz Entertainment Group, and other promoters). When you make a purchase in connection with a performance presented or produced by a third party organization, the Center will provide said third party with the information regarding your purchase. This information may include, but shall not be limited to, your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address, as well as details of your purchase, which may include, but shall not be limited to, the date you purchased your tickets, any offer you responded to, the locations of your seats, and the dollar amount of your transaction.

In order to manage Arsht Center e-mail subscription lists, we retain the names and e-mail address of our e-mail subscribers, as well as other information they may have shared with us (e.g., addresses and phone numbers), logs of e-mails we send, and automatically generated e-mail data used to improve our e-mail communications. This automatically generated e-mail data (generated through simple tools such as “pixel tags” and link redirects) includes:

The recipient’s e-mail client;

Whether the e-mail was opened;

If a link in the message was clicked;

Whether an e-mail was delivered; and,

Whether the e-mail was forwarded; 

If, at any time, you wish to stop receiving our messages, simply click on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each e-mail message.

You may request to be removed from our mailing or phone list at any time. In addition, you may edit personal information in your account; specifically your name, address, phone number, interest preferences and contact preferences through our Web site or by contacting us at the phone number or mailing address listed at the end of this document.

Financial information: the Center will protect any personal financial information that you share with us. If you make a purchase online, we will use your credit card number only to process your payment and will not use it for marketing or demographic purposes. For reasons of security, credit card information is not stored on our Web Server. We will retain order information for our records, but this information is never shared with third parties.

**2\. Personal Information of Minors**

We do not solicit Personal Information from minors. Sites specifically geared toward children will not request any personal or contact information.

**3\. Technology**

We may use "cookie" technology. A cookie is a small amount of data sent by our Web site and stored on your computer's hard drive that our site can read and which helps us keep track of how you use our Web site. Many Web browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but contain an option for you to turn off the cookie acceptance if you prefer. If you turn off acceptance, there may be some features of our Web site that will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly. We do not allow unrelated third parties to set cookies via the Center's Web site.

**4\. Links**

Our Web site may include links to other Web sites. We do not control the privacy policies of the destination sites. Once you leave our servers (you can check where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site that you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from such a site's homepage, you should contact the manager of that site for more information. the Center is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites other than the Center's Web site.

**6\. Comments on Social Media Platforms**

We are pleased to offer our community an opportunity to share diverse opinions and varied points of view on our social media pages - in fact, we encourage it! Our goal is to build community through the arts and, as such, we do require that all comments follow a few basic standards. Comments that are threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic or racist will be removed. We require that all comments are free from profanity and hate speech. All comments should be relevant to the post and remain respectful of other commenters.

**7\. Security and Disclaimer**

Although we use security that we believe to be appropriate to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee that our security precautions will protect against, and we expressly disclaim any liability for, any loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

**8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

the Center, from time to time, may update this policy without prior notice. Changes to this policy will be reflected on the Center's Web site.

**9\. Questions and Suggestions**

If you have any questions or suggestions, please complete an online feedback form or you can contact us at:

The Adrienne Arsht Center for the Performing Arts of Miami-Dade County  
1300 Biscayne Blvd., Miami, FL 33132  
Telephone: 305.949.6722
